# Jon Coulter

#### (412) 418-6834

jonrcoulter@gmail.com http://www.joncoulter.design

Web designer with a passion for building highly usable and great looking websites with the latest technology. I work on a small team and have a lot of experience designing, building, and managing websites for products. Because of the complexity and variety of websites I've worked on I have experience in both PHP and ASP.NET on the back end and my expertise is CSS3/SASS, JS/jQuery, and HTML5 on the front end.

Skills

- HTML 5
- Advanced CSS
- jQuery
- Responsive Web Design User Experience
- Graphic Design

- Adobe Creative Suite
  User Interface Design
  Front-end Development

Experience

#### GrapeCity, Inc.

04 / 2015 - Present

Web Designer

- Planning, design, development, and management of Spread, ActiveReports, ActiveAnalysis, and Dragonfly websites.
- Graphic design for marketing tasks.
- UI design for GrapeCity products.
- Working with developers locally and international in all platforms.

### **GrapeCity**

10 / 2008 - 04 / 2015

Web Designer

- Planning, design, and management of ComponentOne.com, Wijmo.com, ComponentOne Community, GCActiveReports.com, GCSpreadStudio.com, GCActiveAnalysis.com, DeveloperTools.com, and GoXuni.com
- Working with developers locally and international in all platforms.

#### **Bauer Graphics, Inc.**

06 / 2010 - 11 / 2014

Web Designer

Freelance web design for Bauer Graphics clients.

Education

## **Art Institute of Pittsburgh**

2004 - 2008

BS, Graphic Design